tf.org 2006-12-16

# TF.org - The Films :: TF.ORG Privacy Notice - movie download page

TF.ORG knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. **By visiting TF.ORG, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

## **What Personal Information About Users Does TF.ORG Gather?**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at TF.ORG. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Click here to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses TF.ORG. Click here to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at TF.ORG if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
  * **E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from TF.ORG if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please use our User Administration pages to adjust your preferences.
  * **Information from Other Sources** : For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better movie recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next communication more easily.

## **What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as My Movies, local show times, and browsing preferences. 
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of TF.ORG's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

## **Does TF.ORG Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. Thus, for example, TF.ORG does not sell, and will never sell, information about you to external marketers, list brokers, or other third parties without user consent. Nor will we give such information to affiliated businesses or companies that we team up with to provide co-branded or jointly owned offerings unless you choose to take advantage of those offerings, and even then, any sharing of information is limited to information relating to the offering. Further, whenever we deal with user information, we will always comply with applicable laws and regulations in doing so.

We share user information with our parent corporation (Amazon.com, Inc.), the subsidiaries it controls, and as described below. 

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control** : We work closely with our affiliated businesses. In some cases, we will include offerings from these businesses on TF.ORG. In other cases, we may include joint offerings from TF.ORG and these businesses on TF.ORG. You can tell when another business is involved in the offering, and we share user information related to those offerings with that business. 
  * **Agents** : We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Promotional Offers** : Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of TF.ORG users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and e-mail address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please use our User Administration pages to adjust your preferences. 
  * **Business Transfers** : As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy additional services or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is transferred along with the rest of the service or business unit. Also, in the event that The Internet Movie Database Ltd., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will of course be included in the transaction. 
  * **Protection of TF.ORG and Others** : We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of TF.ORG, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

Other than as set out above, you will always receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

## **What About Third-Party Advertisers?**

Our site includes third-party advertising, and some of our advertisers use third-party companies to serve their advertisements that appear on our site.Often, these third-party advertising companies, called "ad networks" or "network advertisers", employ cookie and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to show you ads that are more relevant and interesting to you. We do not provide any user information to them, and we do not have access to or control cookies that may be placed by the ad networks. If you would like more information about the ad networks, including information about how to opt-out of their information collection, the [National Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers useful information on its Web site.

## **How Secure Is Information About Me?**

If you use our subscription service, we work to protect the security of your subscription information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

## **What Choices and Access Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of such TF.ORG features as My Movies and local show times. 
  * You can add or update certain information, such as your e-mail address, by using our User Administration pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please use our User Administration pages to adjust your preferences. (If you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of TF.ORG, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use such important features as My Movies and local show times if you do not use cookies. 
  * Click here to explore products that offer anonymous browsing. In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, [Site Seeing on the Internet](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html). 

## **Children**

TF.ORG is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not submit information about yourself to TF.ORG. 

## **Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit TF.ORG, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at TF.ORG, please send us a thorough description to our help desk, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
